Her recent photos
صورها الأخيرة
[Qi's post] didn't look like selfies.
لم تكن منشورات [تشي] تبدو كصور سيلفي.
So my friend
إذن يا صديقي
suspects she's having an affair.
يشتبه في أنها على علاقة غرامية.
So I'd like to ask you to look into it
لذا أود أن أطلب منكم النظر في الأمر.
and find out who the other person is.
واكتشف من هو الشخص الآخر.
Once you have identified them,
بمجرد تحديدها،
we will meet again.
سنلتقي مجدداً.
Mr. Yin, two people from the Special Administration Bureau are here.
السيد يين، يوجد هنا شخصان من مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
They say they want to buy your collectibles.
يقولون إنهم يريدون شراء مقتنياتك.
I've heard
لقد سمعت
you are interested in that fragment.
أنت مهتم بتلك الجزئية.
Name your price.
حدد السعر الذي تريده.
I just heard
سمعت للتو
that you are with the Special Administration Bureau.
أنك تعمل لدى مكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
Then your tracking methods
ثم طرق التتبع الخاصة بك
must be quite effective.
لا بد أنه فعال للغاية.
I...
أنا...
I have a friend.
لدي صديق.
His wife...
زوجته...
What is wrong with your wife?
ما مشكلة زوجتك؟
Sorry.
آسف.
She is a bit hard of hearing.
إنها تعاني من ضعف السمع قليلاً.
Please go on.
تفضل.
Your friend's
صديقك
wife...
زوجة...
What happened?
ماذا حدث؟
[Open]
[يفتح]
Before I left, I planted a listening device on Yin Che.
قبل أن أغادر، زرعت جهاز تنصت على يين تشي.
This is the cake shop Qi opened herself.
هذا هو متجر الكعك الذي افتتحته تشي بنفسها.
Every Thursday is members' day.
يوم الخميس هو يوم الأعضاء.
She comes in as the store manager for the day.
تأتي إلى المتجر كمديرة للمتجر لهذا اليوم.
Today's Thursday,
اليوم الخميس،
so she might show up.
لذا قد تظهر.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Are you two
هل أنتما الاثنان
on a date here?
هل نخرج في موعد غرامي هنا؟
It does not really look like a date.
لا يبدو الأمر وكأنه موعد غرامي.
It really
إنه حقاً
does.
يفعل.
Your friend?
صديقك؟
Actually, it is my friend's wife.
في الحقيقة، إنها زوجة صديقي.
My friend asked me
سألني صديقي
to help look into a private matter.
للمساعدة في التحقيق في مسألة خاصة.
You're not very familiar
أنت لست على دراية كبيرة
with how investigations are conducted.
فيما يتعلق بكيفية إجراء التحقيقات.
How about this?
ما رأيك بهذا؟
I will find someone to help you.
سأجد شخصًا يساعدك.
You got here pretty fast.
لقد وصلت إلى هنا بسرعة كبيرة.
Of course.
بالطبع.
I always run when it's Nongyu.
أهرب دائمًا عندما يكون نونغيو.
How are you?
كيف حالك؟
Have you recovered yet?
هل تعافيت بعد؟
When I carried you to the hospital last time,
عندما حملتكِ إلى المستشفى في المرة الماضية،
I could tell how light you were.
استطعت أن أدرك كم كنت خفيف الوزن.
You ordered all of this?
هل طلبت كل هذا؟
Nongyu does not eat sour food
لا يأكل نونغيو الطعام الحامض
and she does not like strongly flavored curry.
وهي لا تحب الكاري ذو النكهة القوية.
The soup is best with scallions for aroma.
يُفضل إضافة البصل الأخضر إلى الحساء لإضفاء نكهة مميزة.
How can you not even know this as her husband?
كيف لا تعرف هذا وأنت زوجها؟
So you do remember that I am her husband?
إذن أنت تتذكر أنني زوجها؟
Why do you know me so well?
لماذا تعرفني جيداً؟
When your brother was choosing a husband for you,
عندما كان أخوك يختار لكِ زوجاً،
he tailored everything precisely to your preferences,
لقد صمم كل شيء بدقة وفقاً لتفضيلاتك،
and carefully shaped Lin Juan.
وشكّلت لين جوان بعناية.
It was as brutal as the Special Administration Bureau's daily training.
كان الأمر وحشياً مثل التدريب اليومي لمكتب الإدارة الخاصة.
You make it sound like I have no sense of self.
أنت تجعل الأمر يبدو وكأنني لا أملك إحساساً بذاتي.
What good is knowing all this?
ما فائدة معرفة كل هذا؟
At the fighting tournament that day,
في بطولة القتال التي أقيمت في ذلك اليوم،
Nongyu did not choose you, did she?
لم تختر نونغيو أنت، أليس كذلك؟
Anyway, we warmly welcome Mr. Lin
على أي حال، نرحب ترحيباً حاراً بالسيد لين
to step in and guide our work.
للتدخل وتوجيه عملنا.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Looks like the person we are waiting for today will not show up.
يبدو أن الشخص الذي ننتظره اليوم لن يحضر.
Let's go. Let's head home.
هيا بنا. لنعد إلى المنزل.
Siyuan.
سيوان.
Take your time eating.
تناول طعامك على مهل.
I will head out first.
سأخرج أولاً.
- Be at my place tomorrow at nine in the morning. - Okay.
- كن في منزلي غداً الساعة التاسعة صباحاً. - حسناً.
All of this was ordered for you.
كل هذا تم طلبه من أجلك.
They might also be investigating Qi's affair partner.
وقد يكونون يحققون أيضاً في علاقة تشي الغرامية.
As soon as you get any news about that person,
بمجرد حصولك على أي أخبار عن ذلك الشخص،
inform me right away.
أبلغني على الفور.
Okay.
تمام.
What's wrong with you today?
ما بك اليوم؟
You were so kind to Lin Juan.
لقد كنت لطيفًا جدًا مع لين جوان.
You did it on purpose to provoke me.
لقد فعلت ذلك عن قصد لاستفزازي.
What happened since yesterday?
ما الذي حدث منذ أمس؟
That kind of kindness was not even sincere.
لم يكن ذلك النوع من اللطف صادقاً حتى.
Then why did you not dodge when I kissed you yesterday?
إذن لماذا لم تتفادى قبلتي لك بالأمس؟
Do you think I could have pushed you away?
هل تعتقد أنني كنت قادراً على إبعادك؟
Then I will not take the initiative to kiss you again.
إذن لن أبادر بتقبيلك مرة أخرى.
Unless you say you want it.
إلا إذا قلت إنك تريد ذلك.
I understand.
أفهم.
That counts as him admitting it, right?
هذا يعتبر اعترافاً منه، أليس كذلك؟
That him kissing me yesterday,
أن يقبلني بالأمس،
was not driven by genuine feelings.
لم يكن مدفوعاً بمشاعر حقيقية.
[New update from Qi, a blogger you viewed.]
[تحديث جديد من تشي، المدون الذي شاهدته.]
There's an update from Qi's account.
هناك تحديث من حساب Qi.
Looking for flower shop recommendations.
أبحث عن توصيات لمحلات بيع الزهور.
Qi's flowers...
أزهار تشي...
Could they be for that affair partner of hers?
هل يمكن أن تكون هذه الصور لشريكها في تلك العلاقة؟
Highly recommend Little Lady Flower Shop.
أوصي بشدة بزيارة متجر الزهور "ليتل ليدي".
Order placed.
تم تقديم الطلب.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Excuse me, did someone named Qi place a flower order here?
عفواً، هل قام شخص يُدعى تشي بطلب باقة زهور هنا؟
Sorry, Miss, but we can't just disclose customer information.
معذرةً يا آنسة، لكن لا يمكننا ببساطة الكشف عن معلومات العملاء.
My apologies.
أعتذر.
Biao.
بياو.
What's taking so long?
ما الذي يستغرق كل هذا الوقت؟
Coming.
آت.
Qi's order is about to time out.
سينتهي وقت تنفيذ أمر تشي قريباً.
Hey.
يا.
Please make way for pedestrians.
يرجى إفساح الطريق للمشاة.
Sorry.
آسف.
Jumping out of the car just now was way too dangerous.
كان القفز من السيارة الآن أمراً بالغ الخطورة.
Good thing Lin Juan braked in time.
لحسن الحظ أن لين جوان ضغطت على الفرامل في الوقت المناسب.
I need to rest.
أحتاج إلى الراحة.
Could it be that you pushed yourself too hard just now,
هل من الممكن أنك أرهقت نفسك كثيراً الآن؟
and the virus went out of control?
وخرج الفيروس عن السيطرة؟
Something feels off between you two.
هناك شيء ما ليس على ما يرام بينكما.
Did you argue?
هل تشاجرتما؟
I will go check on him.
سأذهب لأطمئن عليه.
You investigate where Qi's bouquet was delivered,
تقوم بالتحقيق في مكان تسليم باقة زهور تشي،
can you handle that?
هل يمكنك التعامل مع ذلك؟
The inhibitor is in my bag.
المثبط موجود في حقيبتي.
I will help you administer it.
سأساعدك في إدارته.
There is a faster way than that.
هناك طريقة أسرع من ذلك.
You said you would not take the initiative to kiss me.
قلتَ إنك لن تبادر بتقبيلي.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
He's out of control. Instead of soothing him,
لقد خرج عن السيطرة. بدلاً من تهدئته،
she uses an inhibitor.
إنها تستخدم مثبطًا.
Such an inefficient and uncomfortable way to cope.
يا لها من طريقة غير فعالة وغير مريحة للتعامل مع الأمور.
That's strange.
هذا غريب.
It has been a whole day.
لقد مر يوم كامل.
Any progress?
هل من جديد؟
I suspect Nongyu and Xie Xinxu
أظن أن Nongyu و Xie Xinxu
never actually formed a pact.
لم يتم إبرام أي اتفاق فعلي.
Are you sure?
هل أنت متأكد؟
Of course I am not.
بالطبع لست كذلك.
It is just a guess.
إنه مجرد تخمين.
Do not worry.
لا تقلق.
I will look into it properly.
سأبحث في الأمر جيداً.
Do you want me to hold you?
هل تريدين أن أحتضنك؟
No.
لا.
Lin Juan said
قال لين جوان
Qi has a friend who opened a cafe.
لدى تشي صديق افتتح مقهى.
That bouquet
تلك الباقة
was a congratulatory gift for the opening.
كانت هدية تهنئة بمناسبة الافتتاح.
If you feel unwell next time,
إذا شعرت بتوعك في المرة القادمة،
just say it directly.
قلها مباشرة.
Comforting you
أريحك
is written into our contract.
هذا منصوص عليه في عقدنا.
I will
أنا سوف
honor the contract terms.
الالتزام ببنود العقد.
So,
لذا،
as long as it is written into a contract,
طالما أن ذلك منصوص عليه في العقد،
anyone
أي شخص
can receive your comfort, right?
يمكنك الحصول على راحتك، أليس كذلك؟
You're crazy.
أنت مجنون.
Qi?
تشي؟
This is your account, right?
هذا حسابك، أليس كذلك؟
[Rain]
[مطر]
You were investigating me?
هل كنت تحقق معي؟
[After our technical analysis,]
[بعد تحليلنا الفني،]
[the final result shows the photo is 88 percent composited.]
[تظهر النتيجة النهائية أن الصورة مركبة بنسبة 88 بالمائة.]
The technical team said
قال الفريق الفني
Qi's photos were edited composites.
صور تشي كانت صوراً مركبة معدلة.
Why would she
لماذا تفعل ذلك؟
fabricate photos from a boyfriend's point of view?
هل يمكن تزييف الصور من وجهة نظر الحبيب؟
What boyfriend's point of view?
ما وجهة نظر الحبيب؟
He really overthought it.
لقد بالغ في التفكير في الأمر.
I took those photos just to let Yin Che know
التقطت تلك الصور فقط لأُعلم يين تشي
that I was having a great time on my own.
أنني كنت أقضي وقتاً رائعاً بمفردي.
But he assumed
لكنه افترض
you were cheating.
كنت تغش.
I really don't know what to say.
لا أعرف حقاً ماذا أقول.
What we had from the start
ما كان لدينا منذ البداية
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
(شاهد على www.kissasia.co، .be، .org، .net، .id، .xyz)
was just ill-fated.
كان الأمر مجرد سوء حظ.
This is a guaranteed question on the final exam.
هذا سؤال مضمون في الامتحان النهائي.
He was my private tutor back in college.
كان معلمي الخاص في الجامعة.
Here,
هنا،
you need to add the value in the parentheses
يجب عليك إضافة القيمة الموجودة بين القوسين
to this value.
إلى هذه القيمة.
Work on these questions first.
ابدأ بالعمل على هذه الأسئلة أولاً.
In half an hour,
في غضون نصف ساعة،
I will explain them to you.
سأشرحها لك.
♪The sky opens wide…♪
♪ تنفتح السماء على مصراعيها…♪
Maybe it was because he fit my taste perfectly.
ربما كان ذلك لأنه كان يناسب ذوقي تماماً.
I ended up falling for him beyond all reason.
انتهى بي الأمر بالوقوع في حبه بشكل يفوق كل منطق.
♪But still it begins♪
♪لكنها لا تزال تبدأ♪
At first, I thought my quiet feelings
في البداية، ظننت أن مشاعري الهادئة
would fade away on their own with time.
ستتلاشى من تلقاء نفسها مع مرور الوقت.
But Yin Che's family suddenly fell seriously ill.
لكن عائلة يين تشي مرضت فجأة مرضاً خطيراً.
My parents wanted to help me get what I wished for,
أراد والداي مساعدتي في الحصول على ما تمنيته.
so they proposed that as long as we got married,
لذا اقترحوا أنه طالما تزوجنا،
they would lend him money to cover the medical bills.
كانوا يقرضونه المال لتغطية النفقات الطبية.
So,
لذا،
we got married.
تزوجنا.
♪Looking for answers in the dark♪
♪ نبحث عن إجابات في الظلام ♪
♪You're searching endless works of art♪
♪أنت تبحث عن أعمال فنية لا حصر لها♪
♪To find life inside of them♪
♪لإيجاد الحياة بداخلهم♪
But after marriage, we clashed in every possible way.
لكن بعد الزواج، اختلفنا في كل شيء ممكن.
Honey, look.
يا عزيزتي، انظري.
I love animals, but he is allergic to cat fur.
أنا أحب الحيوانات، لكنه يعاني من حساسية تجاه وبر القطط.
Even when it comes to food, we never agree.
حتى عندما يتعلق الأمر بالطعام، لا نتفق أبداً.
I ordered a lot of takeout.
طلبتُ الكثير من الطعام الجاهز.
Do you want to eat together?
هل ترغبون بتناول الطعام معاً؟
No.
لا.
We could not even sleep together.
لم نكن نستطيع حتى النوم معاً.
Let us stay together tonight.
فلنبقَ معاً هذه الليلة.
Did we not agree
ألم نتفق؟
that we only share a bed on Saturdays?
هل يعني ذلك أننا نتشارك السرير فقط أيام السبت؟
There are still two days to go.
ما زال أمامنا يومان.
♪They come, then they leave you♪
يأتون، ثم يرحلون عنك.
Then one day...
ثم في يوم من الأيام...
Okay. Bye.
حسنًا. مع السلامة.
♪But sure to appease you♪
♪لكنها سترضيك بالتأكيد♪
I have a project that requires long-term remote work at home.
لدي مشروع يتطلب العمل عن بعد من المنزل لفترة طويلة.
I need
أحتاج
a quiet space to be alone.
مكان هادئ لأكون فيه بمفردي.
Why don't you
لماذا لا تفعل ذلك؟
take a vacation for a while?
هل ترغب في أخذ إجازة لفترة من الوقت؟
♪Like waving candles in the rain♪
♪كأنك تلوح بالشموع تحت المطر♪
I might as well move out.
ربما من الأفضل أن أنتقل من هنا.
The cake shop just opened,
افتُتح محل الكعك للتو،
and I will be busy for a while anyway.
وسأكون مشغولاً لبعض الوقت على أي حال.
I will help you find a place.
سأساعدك في إيجاد مكان.
He could not even be bothered to pretend anymore.
لم يعد يكترث حتى بالتظاهر.
He told me outright
أخبرني بذلك صراحةً
that he wanted space to himself.
أنه أراد مساحة خاصة به.
So I would not cling to him
لذلك لن أتمسك به
and make him hate me even more.
وأجعله يكرهني أكثر.
I wanted to prove to him
أردت أن أثبت له ذلك
that I could live brilliantly on my own.
أنني أستطيع أن أعيش حياة رائعة بمفردي.
But I could not bear to really stay far away from him.
لكنني لم أستطع تحمل الابتعاد عنه حقاً.
So
لذا
I could only edit photos and pretend I was traveling everywhere.
لم يكن بوسعي سوى تعديل الصور والتظاهر بأنني أسافر إلى كل مكان.
So in truth, you went nowhere at all,
إذن في الحقيقة، لم تذهب إلى أي مكان على الإطلاق.
and kept quietly staying by his side?
وظلت تقف بجانبه بهدوء؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
Up until today,
حتى اليوم،
before I heard the awful news that he thought I cheated,
قبل أن أسمع الخبر المروع بأنه ظن أنني خنته،
I was deeply moved by my own devotion.
لقد تأثرت بشدة بإخلاصي.
♪You close your eyes...♪
♪أغمض عينيك...♪
But I'm clear now.
لكن الأمور واضحة الآن.
Now the safest thing is to divorce as soon as possible.
الآن، أفضل شيء هو الطلاق في أسرع وقت ممكن.
Then what
ثم ماذا؟
are you planning to do next?
ماذا تخطط للقيام به لاحقاً؟
I am going to get my revenge.
سأنتقم.
Mr. Yin.
السيد يين.
There is an answer about Qi's affair partner.
هناك إجابة بخصوص شريك تشي في علاقته الغرامية.
Did she really cheat?
هل خانت حقاً؟
I have sent you the address. Let us talk in person.
لقد أرسلت لك العنوان. دعنا نتحدث وجهاً لوجه.
He.
هو.
Cancel all my plans for tonight.
ألغي جميع خططي لهذه الليلة.
Something came up with Yin Che.
حدث شيء ما مع يين تشي.
You abused your wife, did you not?
لقد أسأت معاملة زوجتك، أليس كذلك؟
I did not abuse her.
لم أسيء معاملتها.
Still lying at a time like this.
لا يزالون يكذبون في مثل هذا الوقت.
Fine.
بخير.
Then you can only be treated as trash
عندها لن يُعاملك أحد إلا كقمامة.
and disposed of.
وتم التخلص منها.
Yin Che.
يين تشي.
Sit down in the chair.
اجلس على الكرسي.
This is the Life Transfer Station.
هذه محطة نقل الحياة.
Things like phones are not allowed in here.
أشياء مثل الهواتف ممنوعة هنا.
I regret to inform you
يؤسفني إبلاغكم بذلك
that you
أنك
are already dead.
هم أموات بالفعل.
Sit down.
اجلس.
So
لذا
what now?
ماذا الآن؟
On to the next life?
إلى الحياة الأخرى؟
Depends on
يعتمد على
how much remorse you show for your crimes.
ما مدى ندمك على جرائمك؟
Either you are processed as scrap in the transfer station,
إما أن يتم التعامل معك كخردة في محطة النقل،
or you open the door behind you
أو تفتح الباب خلفك
and start over as a new person.
وابدأ من جديد كشخص جديد.
♪You smell like something strange♪
رائحتك غريبة!
♪Like wood♪
♪مثل الخشب♪
♪Like wine♪
♪مثل النبيذ♪
♪Like the fading rain♪
♪مثل المطر المتلاشي♪
♪It's not a problem I can fix♪
♪ليست مشكلة أستطيع حلها♪
♪Maybe I'm just meant to be your toy♪
♪ربما أنا مجرد لعبة بالنسبة لك♪